moxi9.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy - Moxi9

We keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will reflect any updates within this notice. 

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy. Any such changes will appear here and become effective immediately. 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any of Moxi9 websites. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Email
  * Address

The aforementioned personal information will only be collected by us and modified by you via our secure network at **https://secure.moxi9.com/**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive user our services as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by a secure login into the clients area. If for some reason you cannot login or have lost your password you can use the "lost password" tool. If that process has failed you may then contact us and to protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. There is a security limit of 1 request per 7 days to protect your privacy.
